<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Tanner Legasse</title><link>https://www.tannerlegasse.com/</link><description>Recent content on Tanner Legasse</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 28 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.tannerlegasse.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Sin and Cosin</title><link>https://www.tannerlegasse.com/projects/sin-cosin/</link><pubDate>Sat, 28 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.tannerlegasse.com/projects/sin-cosin/</guid><description>&lt;h2>Intro&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>This is the first of many planned articles on the topic of demoscene programming.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Demos are self contained artistic presentations that are sometimes punctuated by extremely efficient and small code.
 Demoscene developers were typically restricted to extremely limited hardware and storage mediums. While this is
 hardly the case today, I find it prudent to still approach experimentation and learning with this in mind,
 especially when your average, basic node project contains thousands of packages. Yes, I'm a hater, but there's
 something special there.&lt;br> Join me as I explore the core concepts of demoscene development from the context of a
 modern developer interested in learning what it means to get back to basics and develop such incredible works.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Manual Shopify App Authentication</title><link>https://www.tannerlegasse.com/posts/manual-shopify-app-authentication/</link><pubDate>Sat, 03 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.tannerlegasse.com/posts/manual-shopify-app-authentication/</guid><description>&lt;p>Welcome! This is the first of many blog posts covering Shopify application development that will be published here. You&amp;rsquo;ll follow me through the project agnostic portions of app build I&amp;rsquo;m working through. You&amp;rsquo;ll see a production ready app from concept and setup to go-live.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>If you follow along with this series, you&amp;rsquo;ll see various components take shape, code examples, and a general rundown of why I&amp;rsquo;m making architectural decisions. Here&amp;rsquo;s something I probably don&amp;rsquo;t need to tell you; &lt;strong>I&amp;rsquo;m not perfect. I also don&amp;rsquo;t pretend to be!&lt;/strong> So don&amp;rsquo;t expect brilliant code that stands up against every possible use case and every setting. Expect working code that serves as a foundation for fun experiments, &lt;em>lots&lt;/em> of learning, and real, working apps. In a lot of cases, I&amp;rsquo;ll be encountering problems and matching them to solutions for the first time ever!&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Go URL Shortener</title><link>https://www.tannerlegasse.com/projects/go-url-shortener/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.tannerlegasse.com/projects/go-url-shortener/</guid><description>&lt;h1 id="introduction">Introduction&lt;/h1>
&lt;p>It&amp;rsquo;s 3AM. You need a URL shortener fast. Your boss is breathing down your neck and you have no idea what to do. My new URL shortener is &lt;em>exactly&lt;/em> what you need. Okay, kidding aside, this thing isn&amp;rsquo;t geared toward production environments with high throughput or anything like that. Instead, the goal was to showcase skills that I&amp;rsquo;ve picked up over the past several months in my learning journey with Go. It&amp;rsquo;s been really fun, and this project fit the bill of &amp;ldquo;complex enough to be interesting, not so complex that you program yourself into a hole&amp;rdquo;. The latter will come shortly, but for now I&amp;rsquo;m really pleased with how everything&amp;rsquo;s come out.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Archive</title><link>https://www.tannerlegasse.com/archives/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.tannerlegasse.com/archives/</guid><description>archives</description></item></channel></rss>